Finding aid to Amnesty International's Country Dossiers, Europe, Albania to Estonia.
IDC Publishers
Amnesty International's Country Dossiers, Europe: Albania to Estonia.
1975-2005
IDC Publishers, Hogewoerd 151 P.O. Box 11205 2301 EE Leiden The Netherlands
H-2603
Amnesty International.
Collection of documents from Amnesty International's Research Archives concerning individual countries in Europe.
Container List
- Albania, 1
  - Publications, A
    - The death penalty: Amnesty International report. (Extract), 1979; (ACT 05/03/79); A1 (Microfiche 1)
    - Torture in the eighties. (Extract), 1984; (ACT 04/01/84, p. 207-208); A2 (Microfiche 48)
    - Albania: Amnesty International briefing., 12/1984; (EUR 11/03/84); A3 (Microfiche 48)
    - Albania: Political imprisonment and the law., 1984; (EUR 11/04/84); A4 (Microfiche 48)
    - Albania., 1989; Country survey section of When the State Kills ...'' The Death Penalty v. Human Rights.; (ACT 51/07/89); A5 (Microfiche 96)
  - Annual Report entry, B
    - Amnesty International report 1975-76., B1 (Microfiche 1)
    - Amnesty International report 1977., B2 (Microfiche 1)
    - Amnesty International report 1978., B3 (Microfiche 1)
    - Amnesty International report 1979., B4 (Microfiche 1)
    - Amnesty International report 1980., B5 (Microfiche 22)
    - Amnesty International report 1981., B6 (Microfiche 31)
    - Amnesty International report 1982., B7 (Microfiche 31)
    - Amnesty International report 1983., B8 (Microfiche 42)
    - Amnesty International report 1984., B9 (Microfiche 48)
    - Amnesty International report 1985., B10 (Microfiche 57)
    - Amnesty International report 1986., B11 (Microfiche 65)
    - Amnesty International report 1987., B12 (Microfiche 77)
    - Albania., 1988; Amnesty International report 1988 (covers January to December 1987).; B13 (Microfiche 87)
    - Albania., 1989; Amnesty International report 1989 (covers January to December 1988).; B14 (Microfiche 96)
    - Albania., 1990; Amnesty International report 1990.; (POL 10/03/90); B15 (Microfiche 109)
    - Albania., 1991; Amnesty International Report 1991.; (POL 10/01/91); B16 (Microfiche 118)
    - Albania., 9/7/1992; Amnesty International Report 1992.; (POL 10/01/92); B17 (Microfiche 132)
    - Albania., 1 July 1993; Amnesty International Report 1993.; (POL 10/01/93); B18 (Microfiche 148)
    - Albania., 7 July 1994; Amnesty International Report 1994.; (POL 10/02/94); B19 (Microfiche 165)
    - Albania., 1 July 1995; Amnesty International Report 1995.; (POL 10/01/95); B20 (Microfiche 183)
    - Albania., 18 June 1996; Amnesty International Report 1996.; (POL 10/02/96); B21 (Microfiche 202)
    - Albania., 18 June 1997; Amnesty International Report 1997.; (POL 10/01/97); B22 (Microfiche 222)
    - Albania., 18 June 1997; Amnesty International Report 1997 updates.; (POL 10/03/97); B23 (Microfiche 222)
    - Albania., 17 June 1998; Amnesty International Report 1998.; (POL 10/01/98); B24 (Microfiche 241)
    - Albania., 16 June 1999; Amnesty International Report 1999.; (POL 10/01/99); B25 (Microfiche 260)
    - Albania., 30 May 2001; Amnesty International Report 2001.; (POL 10/01/01); B26 (Microfiche 302)
    - Albania., 28 May 2002; Amnesty International Report 2002.; (POL 10/01/02); B27 (Microfiche 321)
    - Albania., 28 May 2003; Amnesty International Report 2003.; (POL 10/003/03); B28 (Microfiche 346)
    - Albania., 26 May 2004; Amnesty International Report 2004.; (POL 10/04/04); B29 (Microfiche 370)
    - Albania., 25 May 2005; Amnesty International Report 2005.; (POL 10/001/2005); B30 (Microfiche 395)
  - News releases, C
    - Fair trials denied to political prisoners, says Amnesty International report on Albania., 12/12/1984; (EUR 11/05/84); C1 (Microfiche 48)
    - Amnesty International News Release: Amnesty International urges release of detained Albanians., 4/7/1990; (EUR 11/03/90); C2 (Microfiche 109)
    - Albania: Clarification sought on arrest of six members of Greek minority., 9 June 1994; AI News Service 120/94.; (NWS 11/120/94); C3 (Microfiche 165)
    - Albania: Amnesty International concerned about alleged violation of right to fair trial., 11 August 1994; Amnesty International News Service 179/94.; (NWS 11/179/94); C4 (Microfiche 165)
    - Albania: Amnesty International concerned about reports of ill-treatment of Greek lawyers and journalists outside Tirana courthouse., 18 August 1994; Amnesty International News Service 187/94.; (NWS 11/187/94); C5 (Microfiche 165)
    - Albania: Amnesty International writes to President about continuing concerns., 30 September 1994; Amnesty International News Service 229/94.; (NWS 11/229/94); C6 (Microfiche 165)
    - Albania: Amnesty International renews appeal to President Berisha on behalf of ethnic Greeks., 27 January 1995; Amnesty International News Service 21/95.; (NWS 11/21/95); C7 (Microfiche 183)
    - Albania: Police misconduct rewarded with impunity., 20 June 1995; (EUR 11/05/95); C8 (Microfiche 183)
    - Albania: Amnesty International appeals for the release of two prisoners of conscience., 1 August 1995; (EUR 11/10/95); C9 (Microfiche 183)
    - Albania: Government cannot pick and choose who is entitled to human rights., 27 June 1996; (EUR 11/14/96); C10 (Microfiche 202)
    - Albania: Amnesty International calls on the Albanian authorities to bring to justice those responsible for human rights violations., 20 September 1996; (EUR 11/21/96); C11 (Microfiche 202)
    - Albania: Amnesty International calls on President Berisha to release nine prisoners of conscience to mark National Day., 20 November 1996; (EUR 11/30/96); C12 (Microfiche 202)
    - Albania: Human rights should not be violated during state of emergency., 3 March 1997; (EUR 11/06/97); C13 (Microfiche 222)
    - Albania: Briefing on recent developments., 13 March 1997; (EUR 11/09/97); C14 (Microfiche 222)
    - Albania: Amnesty International urgently appeals to all sides in Albania not to kill or torture detainees., 14 March 1997; (EUR 11/10/97); C15 (Microfiche 222)
    - Albania: International community must protect Albanian asylum-seekers., 14 March 1997; (EUR 11/11/97); C16 (Microfiche 222)
    - Albania., 19 March 1997; Italy: Amnesty International repeats its call to protect Albanian asylum seekers.; (EUR 30/01/97); C17 (Microfiche 222)
    - Albania: Death penalty on the way out., 13 December 1999; (EUR 11/03/99); C18 (Microfiche 260)
    - Albania: A disturbing pattern of disregard for basic human rights''., 21 December 2000; (EUR 11/02/00); C19 (Microfiche 281)
    - Albania: political will needed to end torture., 22 May 2001; (EUR 11/03/01); C20 (Microfiche 302)
    - Albania: Ill-treatment of children in custody must stop., 7 March 2002; (EUR 11/04/02); C21 (Microfiche 321)
    - Albania and Macedonia should reject impunity agreements on the International Criminal Court., 16 May 2003; (EUR 05/002/03); C22 (Microfiche 346)
    - Albania: Justice must be delivered to victims of torture and other ill-treatment., 10 June 2003; (EUR 11/004/03); C23 (Microfiche 346)
    - Greece: Immigration control-Human rights abuses against Albanians., 14 November 2003; (EUR 25/008/03); C24 (Microfiche 346)
    - Albania: Inhuman and degrading conditions in police stations., 19 February 2004; (EUR 11/02/04); C25 (Microfiche 370)
    - Albania: What happened to Remzi Hoxha?, 21 October 2004; (EUR 11/04/04); C26 (Microfiche 370)
    - Albania: Disability and the right to marry., 11 November 2004; (EUR 11/05/04); C27 (Microfiche 370)
    - Albania: Fatal injuries suffered by a minor in detention remain unexplained., 16 December 2004; (EUR 11/06/04); C28 (Microfiche 370)
    - Albania: No to impunity for torture and ill-treatment., 1 February 2005; (EUR 11/006/2005); C29 (Microfiche 395)
  - Newsletter entries, D
    - Catholic bishops disappear in Albania., 11/1977; D1 (Microfiche 1)
    - Hoxha announces detention of plotters'' - and an amnesty., 1/1983; D2 (Microfiche 42)
    - Political imprisonment and the law in Albania., 1/1985; D3 (Microfiche 57)
    - Amnesty in Albania., 4/1986; D4 (Microfiche 65)
    - Albania: restrictions on basic human rights relaxed., 7/1990; Amnesty International Newsletter, July 1990.; D5 (Microfiche 109)
    - Albania: Political detainees regularly tortured., 10/1990; Amnesty International Newsletter, October 1990.; D6 (Microfiche 109)
    - Albania: Henrik Gjoka., 12/1990; Amnesty International Newsletter, December 1990 (Campaign for prisoners of the month).; D7 (Microfiche 109)
    - Albania: Political prisoners released., 3/1991; Amnesty International Newsletter, March 1991.; D8 (Microfiche 118)
    - Albania: More than 500 political prisoners freed., 7/1991; Amnesty International Newsletter, July 1991.; D9 (Microfiche 118)
    - Human rights violations in Europe: Albania., 8/1991; Amnesty International Newsletter, August 1991 (Focus on Europe).; D10 (Microfiche 118)
    - Albania: Convicted killers hanged in town square (Ditbardh and Josif Cuko)., 9/1992; Amnesty International Newsletter September 1992 (includes photograph).; D11 (Microfiche 132)
    - Albania: Post-election protesters attacked by police., 1 November 1996; (NWS 21/09/96); D12 (Microfiche 202)
    - Albania: Albania: children ill-treated and tortured by police., 1 February 2003; The Wire, February 2003. Vol. 33, No. 1.; (NWS 21/001/03); D13 (Microfiche 346)
    - Albania: Worldwide appeals: Albania., 1 November 2004; The Wire, November 2004. Vol. 34, No. 10.; (NWS 21/10/04); D14 (Microfiche 370)
    - Albania: Worldwide appeals updates: Albania., 1 December 2004; The Wire, December 2004. Vol. 34, No. 11.; (NWS 21/11/04); D15 (Microfiche 370)
  - General AI material / Background papers, E
    - Intolerance and discrimination on grounds of religion or belief. (Extract), 11/1984; (POL 03/05/84); E1 (Microfiche 48)
    - Albania: General Pardon of 11 January 1986., 2/1986; (EUR 11/01/86); E2 (Microfiche 65)
    - Albania., 4/1986; The imprisonment of persons seeking to leave a country or to return to their own country.; (POL 03/02/86); E3 (Microfiche 65)
    - Albania., 5/1986; Religious Intolerance.; (POL 03/03/86); E4 (Microfiche 65)
    - Albania., 12/1989; AI's concerns at the 46th session of the United Nations Commission on Human Rights.; (IOR 41/13/89); E5 (Microfiche 96)
    - Albania: Update on Albania., 12/1/1990; Weekly Update Service 04/90.; (NWS 11/04/90); E6 (Microfiche 109)
    - Albania., 8/1990; Children: Victims of human rights violations.; (ACT 76/01/90); E7 (Microfiche 109)
    - Albania: Parliament approves draft laws reducing number of crimes punishable by death. In: Death Penalty News, October 1990., 10/1990; (ACT 53/06/90); E8 (Microfiche 109)
    - Albania., 11/1990; Amnesty International's concerns at the 47th session of the United Nations Commission on Human Rights.; (IOR 41/15/90); E9 (Microfiche 109)
    - Albania: Summary of Amnesty international's concerns., 13/12/1990; Weekly Update Service 49/90.; (NWS 11/49/90); E10 (Microfiche 109)
    - Albania: Political prisoners pardoned., 16/1/1991; Weekly Update Service 02/91.; (NWS 11/02/91); E11 (Microfiche 118)
    - Constitutional reform in Albania and Laos., 2/1991; Death Penalty News February 1991.; (ACT 53/01/91); E12 (Microfiche 118)
    - Albania: Authorities announce release of remaining political prisoners., 20/3/1991; Weekly Update Service 11/91.; (NWS 11/11/91); E13 (Microfiche 118)
    - Albania: Update to the paper Albania: Legislative change since May 1990 and Amnesty International 's concerns (Amnesty International Index EUR~11/01/91)''., 6/1991; Concerns in Europe November 1990 - April 1991.; (EUR 01/01/91); E14 (Microfiche 118)
    - Albania: Update on human rights developments and Amnesty International's concerns., 11/1991; Concerns in Europe May - October 1991.; (EUR 01/02/91); E15 (Microfiche 118)
    - Albania: ratifications., 11/1991; Concerns in Europe May - October 1991.; (EUR 01/02/91); E16 (Microfiche 118)
    - Albania., 12/1991; Amnesty International's concerns at the 48th session of the United Nations Commission on Human Rights.; (IOR 41/10/91); E17 (Microfiche 118)
    - Albania: Legislative change since May 1990 and Amnesty International's concerns., 1/1991; (EUR 11/01/91); E18 (Microfiche 118)
    - Albania: Edmond Pojani., 23/4/1991; (EUR 11/04/91); E19 (Microfiche 118)
    - Albania: Mithat Havari: investigation case., 23/4/1991; (EUR 11/05/91); E20 (Microfiche 118)
    - Albania: Moves towards abolition., 2/1992; Europe: Moving towards complete abolition of the death penalty.; (EUR 01/01/92); E21 (Microfiche 132)
    - Mongolia, Albania, Armenia: death penalty statistics., 4/1992; Death Penalty News April 1992.; (ACT 53/02/92); E22 (Microfiche 132)
    - Albania: change of government; the death penalty., 6/1992; Amnesty International concerns in Europe November 1991 - April 1992.; (EUR 01/03/92); E23 (Microfiche 132)
    - Public executions: Albania., 9/1992; Death Penalty News September 1992.; (ACT 53/04/92); E24 (Microfiche 132)
    - Albania., 11/1992; Amnesty International's concerns at the 49th session of the United Nations Commission on Human Rights.; (IOR 41/10/92); E25 (Microfiche 132)
    - Albania: the death penalty; discovery of common graves; constitutional court., 12/1992; Amnesty International's Concerns in Europe May 1992 - October 1992.; (EUR 01/04/92); E26 (Microfiche 132)
    - Albania: Constitutional human rights guarantees; death sentences; freedom of expression., 1 June 1993; Concerns in Europe November 1992 - April 1993.; (EUR 01/01/93); E27 (Microfiche 148)
    - Albania: Idajet Beqiri., 22 September 1993; (EUR 11/04/93); E28 (Microfiche 148)
    - Albania: Human rights abuses by police., 1 October 1993; (EUR 11/05/93); E29 (Microfiche 148)
    - Albania., 1 November 1993; Amnesty International's concerns at the 50th session of the United Nations Commission on Human Rights.; (IOR 41/38/93); E30 (Microfiche 148)
    - Albania: Prisoners of conscience; allegations of police ill-treatment; the death penalty., 1 January 1994; Concerns in Europe May - October 1993.; (EUR 01/01/94); E31 (Microfiche 165)
    - Albania: Arrest or prosecution of journalists followed by presidential pardon; arrest of members of Albania's Greek minority; former Communist Party officials on trial for killing border-crossers; death penalty., 1 June 1994; Concerns in Europe November 1993 - April 1994.; (EUR 01/02/94); E32 (Microfiche 165)
    - Albania: Alleged ill-treatment by police of Arben Memolla and his cousin., 1 October 1994; (EUR 11/02/94); E33 (Microfiche 165)
    - Albania: Jani Stefan Magllara., 1 November 1994; (EUR 11/06/94); E34 (Microfiche 165)
    - Albania: Ill-treatment of Osman Curciali by police., 1 November 1994; (EUR 11/07/94); E35 (Microfiche 165)
    - Albania: Avdi, Ali and Enver Keci, their mother and two sisters., 1 November 1994; (EUR 11/08/94); E36 (Microfiche 165)
    - Albania: Dhimitraq Petro., 1 November 1994; (EUR 11/09/94); E37 (Microfiche 165)
    - Albania., 1 December 1994; Amnesty International's concerns at the 51st United Nations Commission on Human Rights.; (IOR 41/11/94); E38 (Microfiche 165)
    - Albania: Death in custody of Enrik Pajtim Islami., 1 December 1994; (EUR 11/10/94); E39 (Microfiche 165)
    - Albania: Prisoners of conscience and political prisoners; ill-treatment; death following ill-treatment in custody or police shootings; death penalty., 1 February 1995; Concerns in Europe May-December 1994.; (EUR 01/01/95); E40 (Microfiche 183)
    - Albania: Ilir Hoxha., 1 April 1995; (EUR 11/02/95); E41 (Microfiche 183)
    - Albania: Failure to end police ill-treatment and deaths in custody., 1 June 1995; (EUR 11/04/95); E42 (Microfiche 183)
    - Albania: Police ill-treatment of Kujtim Nebiaj, Bukuroshe Nebiaj and Arben Nebiaj., 1 July 1995; (EUR 11/07/95); E43 (Microfiche 183)
    - Albania: Police ill-treatment of Fatmir Gjondeda., 1 July 1995; (EUR 11/09/95); E44 (Microfiche 183)
    - Albania: Police ill-treatment of Gentian Gjolena., 18 July 1995; (EUR 11/06/95); E45 (Microfiche 183)
    - Albania: New legislation; prisoners of conscience; ill-treatment in police custody and deaths following ill-treatment or police shootings., 1 September 1995; Concerns in Europe January-June 1995.; (EUR 01/02/95); E46 (Microfiche 183)
    - Albania: Moratoria on executions., 1 September 1995; Death Penalty News September 1995.; (ACT 53/03/95); E47 (Microfiche 183)
    - Albania., 1 March 1996; Concerns in Europe July - December 1995.; (EUR 01/01/96); E48 (Microfiche 202)
    - Albania: Police ill-treatment of the journalist Fatos Veliu., 1 March 1996; (EUR 11/06/96); E49 (Microfiche 202)
    - Albania: Torture and other ill-treatment of Behar Toska., 25 March 1996; (EUR 11/09/96); E50 (Microfiche 202)
    - Albania: Torture occurring in the context of poor discipline., 1 May 1996; The acceptable enemy'': torture in non-political cases.; (ACT 40/01/96); E51 (Microfiche 202)
    - Albania: Three former senior communist officials sentenced to death (news in brief)., 1 June 1996; Death Penalty News June 1996.; (ACT 53/02/96); E52 (Microfiche 202)
    - Albania: Moratoria on executions., 1 July 1996; Abolition of the death penalty worldwide: developments in 1995.; (ACT 50/07/96); E53 (Microfiche 202)
    - Albania., 1 August 1996; Concerns in Europe January - June 1996.; (EUR 01/02/96); E54 (Microfiche 202)
    - Albania: Sulejman Mekollari and Lirim Veliu: prisoners of conscience., 1 August 1996; (EUR 11/16/96); E55 (Microfiche 202)
    - Albania: Detention and ill-treatment of government opponents - the elections of May 1996., 1 September 1996; (EUR 11/17/96); E56 (Microfiche 202)
    - Albania: Imprisonment of prisoner of conscience Nysret Recica., 18 October 1996; (EUR 11/23/96); E57 (Microfiche 202)
    - Albania: A call for the release of prisoners of conscience., 1 November 1996; (EUR 11/27/96); E58 (Microfiche 202)
    - Albania., 1 March 1997; Concerns in Europe July - December 1996.; (EUR 01/01/97); E59 (Microfiche 222)
    - Albania., 15 April 1997; Out of the margins: the right to conscientious objection to military service in Europe.; (EUR 01/02/97); E60 (Microfiche 222)
    - Albania: Crisis in Albania and the state of emergency., 1 September 1997; Concerns in Europe January - June 1997.; (EUR 01/06/97); E61 (Microfiche 222)
    - Council of Europe responds to threats to resume executions - Albania and Ukraine., 1 March 1999; Death Penalty News March 1999.; (ACT 53/02/99); E62 (Microfiche 260)
    - Albania., 1 April 1999; Concerns in Europe July-December 1998.; (EUR 01/01/99); E63 (Microfiche 260)
    - Albania., 21 August 2000; Europe: Concerns in Europe: January - June 2000.; (EUR 01/03/00); E64 (Microfiche 281)
    - Albania., 1 March 2001; Concerns in Europe July-December 2000.; (EUR 01/01/01); E65 (Microfiche 302)
    - Albania: Torture and ill-treatment - an end to impunity?, 18 May 2001; (EUR 11/01/01); E66 (Microfiche 302)
    - Albania: Torture and ill-treatment: Casesheets., 1 July 2001; (EUR 11/06/01); E67 (Microfiche 302)
    - Albania., 1 September 2001; Concerns in Europe January - June 2001.; (EUR 01/03/01); E68 (Microfiche 302)
    - Albania: End impunity for torturers., 20 November 2001; Children Appeal Leaflets.; (ACT 76/07/01); E69 (Microfiche 302)
    - Albania., 1 December 2001; Greece: Sweep Operation: The alleged ill-treatment and torture of 16-year-old Refat Tafili, an Albanian citizen.; (EUR 25/10/01); E70 (Microfiche 302)
    - Albania: Alleged ill-treatment of detainees by police., 1 May 2002; (EUR 11/06/02); E71 (Microfiche 321)
    - Albania., 30 May 2002; Concerns in Europe Bulletin: July - December 2001.; (EUR 01/02/02); E72 (Microfiche 321)
    - Albania., 1 September 2002; Concerns in Europe January - June 2002.; (EUR 01/07/02); E73 (Microfiche 321)
    - Former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia: Alleged ill-treatment of 27 Albanians in Skopje by Macedonian Police., 1 October 2002; (EUR 65/23/02); E74 (Microfiche 321)
    - Albania: Open letter to members of the Albanian Parliament urging rejection of the impunity agreement with the United States of America on the International Criminal Court., 7 May 2003; (EUR 11/003/03); E75 (Microfiche 346)
    - Albania., 1 October 2003; Concerns in Europe and Central Asia January - June 2003.; (EUR 01/016/03); E76 (Microfiche 346)
    - Albania: inhuman and degrading detention conditions in police stations - steps towards reform., 19 February 2004; (EUR 11/01/04); E77 (Microfiche 370)
    - Albania: Europe and Central Asia: Concerns in Europe and Central Asia: July - December 2003., 1 May 2004; (EUR 01/01/04); E78 (Microfiche 370)
    - Albania:, 1 September 2004; Europe and Central Asia: Summary of Amnesty International's Concerns in the Region January - June 2004.; (EUR 01/05/04); E79 (Microfiche 370)
    - Albania: Obligations under the UN Convention Against Torture - a gap between law and practice., 1 February 2005; (EUR 11/001/2005); E80 (Microfiche 395)
    - Albania: Ending impunity for torture and ill-treatment: Appeal Case: Beqir Kaba., 1 February 2005; (EUR 11/003/2005); E81 (Microfiche 395)
    - Albania: Ending impunity for torture and ill-treatment: Appeal Case: Merita Kola., 1 February 2005; (EUR 11/004/2005); E82 (Microfiche 395)
    - Albania: Ending impunity for torture and ill-treatment: Appeal Case: Eriguert Çeka., 1 February 2005; (EUR 11/005/2005); E83 (Microfiche 395)
    - Albania: Recent military supplies to the region., 5 July 2005; Democratic Republic of Congo: arming the east.; (AFR 62/006/2005); E84 (Microfiche 395)
    - Albania., 1 September 2005; Europe and Central Asia: Summary of Amnesty International's Concerns in the Region: July - December 2004.; (EUR 01/002/2005); E85 (Microfiche 395)
    - Amnesty International's Statements to the 2005 OSCE Human Dimension Implementation Meeting., 20 September 2005; (IOR 30/014/2005); E86 (Microfiche 395)
    - Albania., 1 December 2005; Europe Central Asia: Summary of Amnesty International's Concerns in the Region: January - June 2005.; (EUR 01/012/2005); E87 (Microfiche 395)
- Andorra, 2
  - Publications, A
    - Andorra., 1989; Country survey section of When the State Kills ...'' The Death Penalty v. Human Rights.; (ACT 51/07/89); A1 (Microfiche 96)
  - News releases, C
    - Andorra: Coalition to Stop the Use of Child Soldiers: Fourth country to ratify an international., 5 April 2001; (EUR 12/01/01); C1 (Microfiche 302)
    - Andorra: 30th country to ratify the Rome Statute- Halfway towards the International Criminal Court., 1 May 2001; (EUR 12/02/01); C2 (Microfiche 302)
  - General AI material / Background papers, E
    - Andorra: Death penalty abolished., 10/1990; Death Penalty News, October 1990.; (ACT 53/06/90); E1 (Microfiche 109)
    - Andorra., 11/1990; Western Europe: concerns May 1990 - October 1990.; (EUR 03/02/90); E2 (Microfiche 109)
    - Andorra., 30/1/1991; The death penalty: list of abolitionist and retentionist countries.; (ACT 50/01/91); E3 (Microfiche 118)
    - Andorra: Totally abolitionist., 2/1992; Europe: Moving towards complete abolition of the death penalty.; (EUR 01/01/92); E4 (Microfiche 132)
    - Andorra: accession to four Geneva Conventions., 1 January 1994; Concerns in Europe May - October 1993.; (EUR 01/01/94); E5 (Microfiche 165)
    - Andorra: Ratifications., 1 February 1995; Concerns in Europe May-December 1994.; (EUR 01/01/95); E6 (Microfiche 183)
    - Andorra., 1 March 1996; Concerns in Europe July - December 1995.; (EUR 01/01/96); E7 (Microfiche 202)
    - Andorra: Ratification., 1 June 1996; Death Penalty News June 1996.; (ACT 53/02/96); E8 (Microfiche 202)
    - Andorra: Ratifications., 1 August 1996; Concerns in Europe January - June 1996.; (EUR 01/02/96); E9 (Microfiche 202)
- Armenia, 3
  - Annual Report entry, B
    - Armenia., 1 July 1993; Amnesty International Report 1993.; (POL 10/01/93); B1 (Microfiche 148)